Guide to the Montana State Prison records 1864-1974
Montana Historical Society
- Montana State Prison
  - Prisoner Records
    - Prisoner description sheets: E.C. Abbie, Laurence Abel, Wilfred Abel, William Acker, Charles Ackerley, Fred Ackies, John Adair, Alfred Adams, J.F. Adams, Edward Adams, J.F. Adams, Joseph Adams, William G. Adams, William W. Adams, Frank Addler, Ben Aerts, Herman Aho, Charles Ainsworth, Thomas Ainsworth, Archie Aker, Harry Albert, Robert Albertson, Ben Aldridge, Carl Alexander, John Alguire, Ed Allard, Charles Allen, Charles C. Allen, George Allen, George Allen, Jack Allen, Jack C. Allen, James Allen, Joe Allen, Joe Allen, John Allen, Murl Allen, P.E. Allen, R.T. Allen, Samuel F. Allen, Ted Allen, William Allen, Robert Alley, Arnold Alsup, Alyea Bert, Henry Amend, William Amrin, August J. Anacker, Andrew Anderson, Claude Anderson, David Anderson, Elmer Anderson, Frank Anderson, Fred Anderson, Jack Anderson, John Anderson, Lenard Anderson, Nels Anderson, Pete Anderson, Pete Anderson, W.E. Anderson, Walter Anderson, William Anderson, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 44/1)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Fillipo Andonetti, Norman Andrews, Steve Andropenkl, Gust Andros, Peter Anest, Antone Matt, Louis Anzevine, Carl Applegate, Josi Arcega, William Archibald, O.L. Armour, A.S. Armstrong, Dolphus Armstrong, Cyrus Eugene Armstrong, George Armstrong, George Armstrong, LeRoy Armstrong, Arthur J. Arnold, John Arnold, W.J. Arnold, William Arnoldy, Ramon Aronbarra, Charles Arseneau, J.W. Ashley, Louis Ashley, Charles Ashlock, George Assiminis, J.C. Atherton, Alexander Atkinson, George Atkinson, Frank Augustine, Fred Aurich, Lee Austin, Basilio Avergo, John Avouis, Earl R. Awes, John Ayers, Willis Ayers, Howard Ayrea, Pat Azure, Lester Babb, Clarence A. Babcock, Reuben Babcock, George Backer, George Backman, Blagoji Blackroch, Mike Badorek, George Marvin Baggs, Fred Bailey, George Bailey, George Bailey, Joseph Bailey, M.E. Bailey, W.F. Bailey, Frank Baker, Frank Baker, Frank Baker, Frank Baker, George Baker, H.D. Baker, James A. Baker, Louis Baker, O.C. Baker, Walter Baker, William E. Baker, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 44/2)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Ezra Monroe Balcom, David M. Baldwin, Harry Baldwin, Ivan Balen, E.D. Baley, John Balinski,Bob Ball, Byran Ball, Robert Ball, Peter James Baltzer, Norris D. Bancroft, George W. Bangesser, N. Bannon, B.P. Barber, William Barber, Al Barden, Rade Barich, U.S. Bariel, Bryant Barker, Ernest Barkier, John Barkstrom, Alexander Barlow, George Barnaby, Leo Barnaby, Arnold Barnes, Walter Barnes, E.M. Barnett, J.J. Barnett, Kenneth Barnum, Charles R. Barr, Robert Barr, W.J. Barr, A.J. Barrett, Albert Barret, James Barrett, Clifford Barry, David P. Barry, Michael Barry, Mike Barry, John Barthalemew, William Bartiniscke, Cal Bartlett, Champion B. Bartron, Edward M. Bassford, Frank Bastien, Eugene Battle, A.H. Battnaue, Samuel Bauchamb, H.D. Bauer, John Bauer, Otto Bauer, Otto Boumann, Herman Bausch, Charles Bazel, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 44/3)
    - Prisoner description sheets: George E. Beach, Samuel Beach, John Beadle, Arthur L. Beale, Clyde Beals, James Beard, William E. Beard, J.J. Beasley, Alex Beaucrin, Fred Beaudry, Hector Victor Beaudry, Welcome Bebout, Frank Bechinski, Harry Beck, Henry Beck, W.L. Beck, F.M. Beckman, William Beech, Harry A. Beeler, Mike Behung, Samuel Belch, Frank Belgard, Tom Belgard, James Belgarde, Patrick Belgrade, William Belgrade, Rayley Belich, Albert Belm, Emmett P. Bell, George Bell, Harry Bell, Lee Bell, William Belland, Morase J. Belmont, Martin J. Belter, Tony Bender, Harry Benham, Theo H. Benike, Frank Benka, Charles Bennett, Edward Bennet, George Bennet, George Bennett, T.M. Bennett, Vaughn Q. Bennett, Frank Bennon, Louis Bercic, Simeon Bercier, Andrew Berg, George Berg, Julius J. Berg, Samuel Berg, Pat Berger, William Bergman, F.J. Bergold, Ed Berkhardt, Charles C. Bernard, Fred Bernhard, Harry Bernstein, Elmer Bertilson, John M. Bertrand, Mike Bergan, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 44/4)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Albert Bess, Elijah Bess, William A. Bevan, Otto Biastock, Leroy Bickford, William Bicknell, Rollie D. Bigley, J.J. Billick, Nick Billin, Leslie Billingsley, George Billman, Frank Bingaman, Peter Binsfelt, Frank Bird, Gunder Birkeland, Earl Bishop, Clarence Black, John O. Black, John Black, L.E. Black, Lester I. Black, Mehael Black, Samiel C. Black, O.A. Blackburn, W.A. Blackburn, Albert Blair, George D. Blair, George W. Blair, Frank Blake, George Blake, Leo H. Blake, Walter Blake, Elmer H. Blanchard, F.E. Blanchard, Anton Blas, Tony Blass, Toney Belish, Walter Blevins, A.E. Blixt, A.F. Blodgett, Jack Bondell, Edward Blue, Jess Blue, Steven Boblit, Wilber Boblit, Charles Bodding, Frederick Herman Boden, Albert Bodine, Joe Bogaski, Fritz Bogatz, Joseph Bogen, Moses Bohanen, John Boland, A.C. Bolduc, Frank Bolduc, Mike Bolich, Lewis Bollinger, A.C. Bolton, Isaac Bonepart, Joe Bonerba, Dan Bonners, J.S. Bonner, William Bonning, Dan T. Boone, Ira M. Booth, Samuel M. Booth, Louis Boppre, Maurice Boster, Robert Bozwell, R. Bothwell, A.D. Botts, Alfred D. Botts, Nathan H. Bouge, P.P. Boukind, George Bourdon, Urbain Bourgaut, Ernest Bowen, J.M. Bower, Max Bower, George Bowman, Raymond Boy, Hugh R. Boyd, Robert Boyd, Jess Boydson, Alex Boyer, Dexter Boyer, William Boyer, Glenn Boys, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 45/1)
    - Prisoner description sheets: C.R. Bradford, Sam Bradisee, Budwin Bradley, E.J. Bradley, Joseph Bradley, S.W. Bradley, Fred Bradshaw, William Bradshaw, Frank Brady, Joseph Brady, Joe Brady, Thomas Brady, George Brando, T.J. Brandon Jr., Jess Brangetto, Charles Brannigan, Melvin Bratcher, Albert Earl Bray, Martin Bray, Henry Breeden, Andrew H. Brenick, James Brennan, James W. Brennan, John Brennan, Robert H. Brennan, Walter Brennan, Charles L. Bresse, John Bresnahan, Leroy Brickley, Albert Bridge, H.G. Brien, Claude Briggs, William Brindle, Charles Brinkley, James E. Britton, J.B. Britz, Harry Broadwater, William D. Brodock, Homer Brokaw, Albert Brooke, J.L. Brooks, James C. Brooks, Lester Brooks, M.S. Brooks, R.M. Brooks, Jay Brough, Ora Brower, A.D. Brown, Al Brown, Albert Brown, Charles Brown, Charles E. Brown, Charles L. Brown, Clarence Brown, E. Brown, Frank Brown, Frank Brown, Frank Brown, George Brown, H.M. Brown, Harry Brown, Harry Brown, Harry S. Brown, Harry Brown, James Brown, James Brown, James Brown, Joseph J. Brown, Joe Brown, John Brown, John Brown, Joseph Brown, M.L. Brown, Manual Brown, Miles E. Brown, Patrick Brown, Ray Brown, Walter Brown, William Brown, William Brown, William Brown, Z. Dana Brown, William Brown, Wilfred Browning, Chester Brudnich, J.E. Brumeger, Damas Bruneau, John Brunk, Arthur Bryan, Ernest E. Bryan, John Bryan, Roy Bryan, Art Bryant, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 45/2)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Lester Buchanan, William Buchfinck, P.M. Buck, Richard Buck, Donald Buckley, Ed Buckley, Morris Buckley, Charles Buckman, Neil Buckney, August Budau, Elmer Budinger, George Budinger, Manuel Buleda, Abraham A. Buller, Bert Buller, W.J. Bunce, Archie Bunch, Charles C. Bunn, Thomas Burans, William Burch, A.C. Burchfield, Lyle Burgett, James Burk, John Burk, Charles Burke, Emmett Burke, Emmet J. Burke, F.J. Burke, James Burke, James J. Burke, Joseph J. Burke, Michael H. Burke, R.H. Burke, William Burke, Herman Burkhardt, Ellsworth Burling, R.C. Burnett, John Burney, Andrew Burnick, Charles Burns, Edd Burns, Frank Burns, Frank Burns, George Burns, James Burns, John Burns, Otto Burns, Robert Burns, Susie Burns, Thomas Burns, William Burns, Joseph Burshia, Frank Burt, Ambrose Burton, Claude Burton, E.S. Burton, George W. Burton, John Burton, M.S. Burton, George Burtone, George A. Burtt, Clarence Bush, Henry Bushman, Herbert George Buss, Ronald C. Butard, Elmer Butler, Harry Buttler, M.J. Butler, Clayton Butts, Mathew Buymas, Charles E. Bybee, Dwight Byers, Frederick Byrd, Earl J. Byrne, Stephen Byrne, James Byrnes, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 45/3)
    - Prisoner description sheets: John J. Cahill, U.R. Cahling, G.G. Cain, John Cain, John T. Cain, Erni Calcaterra, Arthur Calder, C.J. Calder, Eugene Caldwell, W.C. Caldwell, Sam Calin, Arthur Callahan, E.F. Callahan, Mat Calivan, John Calvert, William Calvert, Angus Cameron, Harry Cameron, Juan Camp, Nick Campanello, Archie Cambell, William H. Cambell, Joe Cannon, Tom Canty, Charley Capalette, Charles Caplett, Ben Carciona, Joe Wilson Cardston (alias Carson Crosby), Patrick Carey, Edward Carlson, Magna Carlson, O.J. Carlson, Peter Carlson, Sells Carmen, Herschel Carmichael, Arthur Carney, J.C. Carney, John Carney, Edward O. Carpenter, Frank Carpenter, Arthur Carr, Jess Carr, John T. Carr, Robert Carr, Herbert Carriveau, Hubert Carriveau, John Carriveau, Leo Carslisle, E.J. Carson, Frank W. Carson, H.R. Carson, J.L. Carson, James Carson, Roberts Carson, Clarence Carter, John W. Carter, William Carter, Chester S. Casey, Jim Casey, Pat Casey, Thomas Casey, Tom Cason, James W. Cass Jr., Lewis S. Cass, Henry Cassidy, John Caterni, Claude Catliff, Lon Caton, William L. Cavanaugh, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 45/4)
    - Prisoner description sheets: John Cenfrey, Joseph Cerverin, Ladinger F. Chadek, J.D. Chamberlin, Charles E. Chaney, Merrick Chapin, Allan Chapman, Fred Chapman, George Chapman, Harold Chapman, Mike Chapman, Roman Charlie, Eddie Chase, Fred Chase, Earl Chatwood, Bill Cherry, J.L. Chevigny, George Chicoin, George Chisler, Duncan Chisholm, Joe H. Chounard, Eugene Choquette, John Choquette, Christian Chrisman, Fred O. Christensen, Louis Christiansen, Viggo Christensen, W.V. Christie, Laro Chrono, Theodore Chronopolous, Bert Clarey, A.L. Clarke, Charles Clark, Charlie Clark, Ed Clark, Ed Clark, Frank Clark, Fred Clark, H.C. Clark, Harry Clark, James W. Clark, Joe Clark, Joseph Clark, Lewis Clark, Riginald Clark, Roy Clark, Tex Clark, Tony Clark, William Clark, William Clark, George Clatworthy, William Clausen, Peter Clay, John E. Clayborne, George Clemons, James Clergy, George Cleveland, E.G. Clifford, T.D. Clifton, W.E. Clinton, William D. Clites, George Cloppa, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 45/5)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Ray A. Cobban, John Cobell, John Coble, Arthur Coe, Ed Coffey, Isaac Cohen, Louis S. Cohen, M.E. Cohen, Joseph Codner, Frank Cohn, George Colamber, James Colbert, Charles Cole, Coleman Cole, George Cole, Homer Cole, James Cole, R.L. Cole, Raymond Cole, W.R. Cole, Fred Coleman, M. Coleman, Sam Coleman, T.P. Coleman, J.C. Collans, Glen Collard, A.C. Collins, C.J. Collins, Francis Collins, Frank Collins, Harry Collins, John Collins, R.R. Collins, Tom Collins, George Columbus, George Colver, Steve Combs, William Comerford, Roger Conant, George Conkals, Frank Conley, John Conlon, Jack Conn, C.A. Connell, Dan Connell, Charles Connelly, Pat Connelly, Dayton Conniff, Daniel Connors, J.D. Conners, James D. Conners, J. Conor, Thomas Conrad, Bidel Consillis, Archibald H. Constable, William H. Constantine, John Conway, Henry Cooch, Harold Cook, Henry Cook, William T. Coon, Ben R. Cooper, D.E. Cooper, Dan Cooper, Frank Cooper, J.H. Cooper, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 46/1)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Robert Copes, William Copeland, John Copper, Charles Copple, Robert Copple, Clyde Corbly, John Cornell, Peter Cornish, Lavern Cornwell, Samuel Cornwell, Thomas Cornwell, James Correll, Carl Corso, James W. Cosgriff, Frank Costello, Ward Cottrell, Frank Courtney, Arthur Cox, Charles Cox, J.O. Cox, Jesse R. Cox, Walter Cox, Tony Coy, John Craig, A.E. Cramer, William Crampton, Lloyd Crandall, James Crane, John Crane, C.F. Cranford, Fred Crawford, Guss Crawford, Joe Crawford, Conelius Crean, Edward Eugene Crepeau, George Cress, E. Cresson, George Cresswell, Albert Crimer, J.A. Crisler, Thomas Critch, John S. Critchlow, Giovani Croce, Frank Crockett, M.J. Cronin, E.W. Crooks, Harold B. Cross, Conn Crosser, William Crouse, Oner L. Crow, James Crowley, John M. Crown, William Cullen, James Culley, Ray Cullison, Frank Cummings, John Cummings, Kenneth W. Cumming, James Cummings, Theodore Cummings, William Cummings, Louis Cundiff, Schuyler H. Cundiff, R. Charles Curd, H.A. Curran, Henry Curran, Colen Quinton Currie, J.W. Curry, Joseph Curry, Walter Curry, William Curry, Dick Curtin, John Curtin, Frank Curtis, Gerald Curtis, Albert Cutland, R.F. Cutler, Clarence Cyphert (alias Paddy The Pig), Henry Cyr, John Cyr, Frank Cyriax, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 46/2)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Frank Deams, Martha Deams, Carl Dahn, Charles Dalley, Clark Dalby, Glen Dale, A.L. Daley, John Dallas, Ross Dalton, William Dalzell, Alfred E. Daly, James Damon, Charles Francis Daniels, Fred Daniels, Bertha Darcy, Alfred Darces, George Darling, James Darling, Frank Dasting, Ray Daugherty, Lee Davis, Joe Daunes, David Wayne, Charles Davenport, E.J. Davenport, Sam Davey, Frank Davidson, George Davidson, Andrew Davis, Arthur Davis, Charles Davis, Charles E. Davis, Claude Davis, E.C. Davis, Ed Davis, Eddie Davis, George Davis, Ida Davis, Jeff Davis, John Davis, John Davis, Lee Davis, Pat Davis, W.M. Davis, Walter Davis, William Davis, William Davis, C.W. Dawe, William Dawn, Charles E. Dawson, Charles E. Dawson, Ed H. Day, Joe Day, Fred Dean, Kenneth Dean, Fred DeAngelis, Fred Dearborn, Gerald L. Decker, John A. Decker, Thomas DeFries, George W. DeGolier, Eustachro DeGuidice, Dave Deguiles, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 46/3)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Frank Delamere, Fred Delaney, Jesse Delaney, Thomas Delano, William Delmore, Fred DeLong, Joe DeLong, James E. Delp, Tony Delzetti, Frank Delvar, John Demars, A. Demayo, Pedre Demetrof, J.W. Deming, Jack Dempsey, Ed Demus, Walter E. Denney, F.C. Dennis, Frank Denny, Fred Leroy Denny (alias Edward Hanahan), Harry Denny, Giacomo Dente, Harry Denton, William Denton, Joe DePoe, Charles Dero, Joseph Deschamp, Elmer G. Devaul, Martin Deveney, Lee Dever, Thomas Devine, Harry A. Devon, James Dechon, John Dewitt, Thomas F. Dewitt, Augalo Dibene, John Dick, A.C. Dickens, Emery Dicksen, Tony Diedtman, Harry Deitch, Louis Dieziger, Jesse Dills, Joseph Dilly, Arthur Dingle, Cyrel F. Dinsmore, Carlo Dixon, James Dixon (alias Richard Mills), Jay Dixon, Sam Dixon, William Dixon, Bob Dobrich, Berry Doby, Otto John Doctor, Patrick Dodd, C.W. Dodson, James Dodson, John Doe, John Doe, M.J. Doepker, Dennis Dolan, James Dolan, Edward Dolmont, David Dominguez, Marcelino Dominguez, Henry Domnisse, Toy Don, Clarence W. Donaldson, James Donegan, William Doney, William Doney, Frank Donlan, Rolla Donley, Jack Donehue, James Donovan, James Donevan, John Donovan, William Dooley, John Doran, Louis Dorion, J.W. Dorman, James Dornan, Charles Dorsey, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 46/4)
    - Prisoner description sheets: W.H. Dotson, Bob Dossen, Louis Dewey Dotson, Mason Doughty, Howard Douglas, J.W. Douglas, Tom Douglass, E.W. Dowell, Ira G. Downer, J.G. Doyle, John Doyle, John Doyle, Thomas Doyle, Tony Doyle, C.E. Droubay, Charles Drew, John Driscoll, Raymond Driscell, Edward Drummond, Louis Dubois, George Dudack, C.L. Duff, Ed Duffy, Ed Duffy, John Duffy, George Duhl, Frank Duignan, J.J. Dumas, Fred Dumont, Charles Duncan, James Dunford, George Duncan, J.C. Duncan (alias H.C. Smith), Frank Dunham, Abner S. Dunlap, Robert Dunlap, Frank Dunham, Lee Dunn, James Dunne, Harry Dunstruth, John Duquette, William Durbin, Homer Duleth, W.C. Dutron, Benedict T. Duvall, Jack Dwyer, John Dwyer, John Dwyer, Thomas Dwyer, George Dyer, Roy Dyer, Carl Eaden, Dr. Ray E. Easterday, William Eaton, O.W. Eddington, Carl H. Eddleman, John Eder, L.R. Edgerton, Reuben Edstrum, Arthur Edwards, Daniels Edwards, Frank Edwards, H.W. Edwards, Joseph Edwards, Lee Edwards, Roy Edwards, Robert H. Egan, Frank Egen, Charlie Eggert, Claud Eggert, Jack Ehrett, P.G. Eitner, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 46/5)
    - Prisoner description sheets: James Elem, Joseph Elkins, Alex Ellery, A.W. Elliiott, Charles Elliott, John Elliott, J.B. Ellis, John Ellis, Sidney Ellis, William Ellis, William Ellis, Nick Ellis, Albert Elsworth, Frank Eltz, Harry Elvey, O.E. Elwood, Joe Emily, Jake Emerson, Ralph Waldo Emerson, Wilbur Emerson, J.P. Emmerson, William Emmett, Jacob Engle, Edward Englehardt, James English, John A. Enoch, Josephine Enoex, Herman Erickson, John Erickson, Peter Erlandsen, George Erny, Pete Ervik, Herman Erzinger, A. Eschback, Harry Esklund, Leland Eslick, Jackson Eslinger, Joseph Esper, J.H. Esterbrook, Frank Estes, Theodore Evano, A. Evans, A.E. Evans, Charles Evans, Clyde Evans, Frank Evers, Joe Evans, John Evans, Paul Evans, Robert Evans, Roy Evans, Frank Evers, Charles Ewing, John Ewing, W.H. Ewing, Mike Eynick, Ray Fahnlender, Smith Farley, Fred Farlinger, Eugene Farnum, Edward J. Farrell, Joe Farrel, Louie Farrow, Charles Faulkner, Egrida Jalli Faunacci, Ed Fay, Frank Fay, Walter E. Fegl, Adolph Fellensick, Joseph Fennell, George Forgey, Jim Ferguson, Martin Ferkovich, James Ferrari, Louis Ferris, Thomas Ferris, Samuel Ferry, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 47/1)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Fred J. Fielder, Jack Fields, Olivet Fields, Mike Figarella, James Findlay, John Fink, Louis Fink, John Finkbeiner, Antoine Finley, John Finn, Sarah K. Finn, Burt Fisher, Harry Fisher, Herbert Fisher, Herbert Fisher, James Fisher, Martin Fisher, Walter Fisher, Fin Fitch, George G. Fitzgerald, Joe Fitzgerald, W. Fitzgerald, William Fitzgerald, John Flagg, Henry Flaharty, John Flannigan, E.A. Flavell, George Fleir, James T. Fleming, Frank Flibotte, M.L. Flood, Frank Flor, John Floren, Fred Flowers, W. Floyd, Clarence Flynn, J. Flynn, John Flynn, John Flynn, John Flynn, Dan Foley, John Foley, R.H. Foley, Thomas Foley, Thomas J. Foley, Gordon Folkstad, Robert Folster, Toy Foo, Florence Ford, Frank Ford, J.J. Ford, Oscar Ford, Patrick Ford, C.L. Forde, John Foreman, Joe Fornell, Charles Fors, Enoc Forse, Frank F. Forster, William A. Forsyth, Henry Fort, David Foss, Edward Foster, Junius Foster, Leander Foster, Leander Foster, Monroe Foster, Richard Foster, William Fountain, Som Kong Fow, Louis L. Fowler, Mike Fox, Theodore A. Fox, James H. Frank, Charles Franklin, James Franklin, Charlie Fraser, Ben Freeman, Elmer E. Freeman, Randall L. Freeman, George Freestone, Paul Freeze, Carlos Frentez, Leopold Friedman, Albert Fritsh, Harry Fritsch, Arthur M.E. Froembling, E.C. Frye, L.H. Frye, Thomas Fuji, Max Fukelman, J.R. Fuller, Ralph Fuller, Louis Fundinger, J.F. Furlong, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 47/2)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Paul Gable, Fritzof P. Gabriel, Grover Gaffney, Thomas Gaffney, Thomas Gaffney, Shannon Gage, Matt Gaggio, E. Gagnier, Gust Caimos, Ernest Galavig, David Gale, Frank Gale, Stewart Galloway, Barney Gannon, Lloyd Ganser, Alfred Garcia, Felix Garcia, Fred Garcia, John Gardipee, Charles Gardner, Hobart Gardner, Thomas A. Gardner, William M. Gardener, Albert Garier, Arthur Garland, Charles Garlock, Irving Garlock, Robert Garney, A.B. Garrett, Earl Garrett, Herman Gartro, Mike Garvey, Samuel B. Caskill, A.J. Gates, L.C. Gatewood, Benjamin Gathanay, Phillip Gavin, Phillip Gavin, Steve Gaydash, Thomas Gearhart, Ray Gehlen, Joe Gelsleichter, Arthur Genereaux, Homer Louis Gennetti, Mike George, Nick George, Paul George, Sam Gholson, Albert Giadush, George Gibbs, Sam Gibbs, Charles Gibson, George W. Gibson, John Gibson, Tom Gibson, August Gusbrecht, Ed Gieske, Gil Antanacio, W.E. Gilbert, Will Gilbert, Lottie Giles, William Giles, Mike Gilhooley, John Gill, George Gillette, H.R. Gilette, Walter H. Gillette, W. Mayhew Gillies, William Gillon, George Gilmore, Theodore Gilman, Harry L. Gilmore, Tom L. Gilmore, Walter Gilmore, Frank Gilstrap, Walter Gilmore, Alfred J. Kilroy, Frank Gilstrap, James Ginnan, John B. Giovanetti, Lorenzo Giovannini, J. Henry Glasspool, Arthur Glatt, Martin Gleason, Mike Glennon, John Glokski, Melville A. Glynn, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 47/3)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Charles Gorr, Mike Gocni, Harry Goddard, Harold Godfrey, Gus Godley, Dennis Groggin, Mike Groggin, William Goins, Robert Gomerson, Andrew Gomes, Ben Gomez, George Gondeiro, Joe Gonzalig, Mark Good, Jerry Goodwin, Meyer Goodman, Steve Goodrich, George Goodrow, Frank Goodwin, Jack Gordon, John T. Gordon, William Gordon, Louis Gorman, Fred Gould, Thomas Gould, Harry Grady, George Graff, George Graham, John A. Graham, Milton Graham, Smokey Graham, Milford Grainger, Nelson Grandchampe, Harry Grandon, Carl Granger, Alexander Grant, Charles M. Grant, J.V. Grant, Martin Grasswick, Martin Gravelle, Alexander Gray, Matthew A. Gray, Thomas Gray, Tom Gray, Joe Grebenc, Harry Green, Sidney Green, Fred Greenbeck, B.A. Greer, J.G. Greer, G.L. Gregory, Fred Warren Grey, James Grey, Tom Grey, Harry Griffen, George Griffin, John Griffin, John Griffin, John Griffin, John W. Griffin, Nathaniel Griffin, Thomas Griffin, William Griffin, William Griffin, J.A. Griffith, William B. Griffith, Robert Franklin Grimsley, James Grinder, Charles L. Griswold, Earl H. Griswold, Malcolm Griswold, Joe Grovel, Lynn Groom, Alvin Grover, John Grow, Albert Grube, David Guerra, Clarence Guest, Ernest Guidette, Alphonse Guie, Lee Guiear, Andrea Guigni, George Guillfoyle, Alex Guynn, Robert Gumerson, Peter Guss, Ernest R. Gust, Harlan Guynn, Thomas Gwynn, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 47/4)
    - Prisoner description sheets: C.E. Haag, Oscar Haase, Harry Hackett, Albert Haddock, Edwin A. Haderli, Charles A. Haffeman, Nels Hageland, William B. Hagewood, Y. Hagiwara, Jacob O. Hakala, G.W. Hale, William Hale, Ed Haley, Jack Haley, Thomas Haley, John Hale, Frank Halferty, Charles Hall, Clinton Hall, Frank Hall, Frank C. Hall, Fred Hall, James E. Hall, John Hall, Lewis Hall, Martin Hall, Mitchell Hall, Sam Hall, W.H. Hallum, George Halpin, Joseph Halq, Uno Halstrom, Pete Holtzman, Olaf Halverson, Walter Hamelau, Dave C. Hamilton, Fred Hamilton, James Hamilton, Floyed Hamlin, George Hamm, Charles Hammer, Guy Hammond, Wade Hampton, James Haniafian, Frank M. Hankin, Barney Hanlen, Charley Hanley, S.L. Hanley, W.G. Hanna, David Hannah, Frank Hanneck, William Hannula, Helmer Hansen, John Hansen, Julius M. Hansen, Magnor Hansen, Fred Hanson, Harold Hanson, Henry Hanson, Jack Hanson, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 48/1)
    - Prisoner description sheets: I.W. Herbert, George Harbour, Ed Harding, William Hardy, T.J. Hargrove, Henry Harig, John Harrington, John Harrington, John Harrington, B.O.P. Harris, Bertram Harris, Charles Harris, D.H. Harris, E.O. Harris, Francis H. Harris, Frank F. Harris, George Harris, George Harris, George Harris, George Harris, George Harris, L.H. Harris, J.B. Harris, Jack Harris, Joseph Harris, Monte Harris, William Harris, William Harris, William Harris, William Edward Harris, Wilson A. Harris, Frank Harrison, George A. Harrison, Mack J. Harrison, W.E. Harrison, Will Harrison, Eugene Harroll, F.P. Hart, James Hart, John Hart, Joseph Hart, Roy Hart, Thomas Hart, Wade G. Hart, William Hart, Howard Hartley, Charles Hartman, Charles Hartman, George Hartman, William Hartman, Fred Hartness, John J. Hartwell, Dave Harvey, George Harvey, Harry Harvey, John Harvey, William Harvey, Frank Harwell, Charles S. Hash, Glen Hash, John Hasek, George C. Hastings, Charles Hatcher, Leo Hatcher, Roy W. Hatfield, Thomas Hatfield, James Hatton, Albert Haubrich, Ed Havens, Ola A. Haverson, George Haverly, Jules Hawgyt, James V. Hawks, George M. Hayden, Oscar Hayden, John G. Hayes, Louis Hayes, Bartle Hayfield, John Hayfield, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 48/2)